hydroone.com 2009-06-20

# Hydro One : Privacy Policy

Home > Privacy

**Hydro One's Commitment to Privacy**

Protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your Personal Information is a standard by which Hydro One conducts its business. As the largest electricity delivery company in Ontario, the collection, use and disclosure of customers' Personal Information is fundamental to our day-to-day business operations and as such, we strive to provide you with the best customer service. This includes respecting your privacy and treating you fairly.

Hydro One has established a Privacy Code (PDF 54 KB - aussi disponible en français) to inform you about our practices and procedures concerning the collection, usage and disclosure of your Personal Information. It tells you the ways we ensure that your privacy and the confidentiality of your Personal Information are protected.

Should you wish to make a request for information under the Ontario Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Legislation, please complete the FOI Request Form and forward to: S. Lawrance, Manager - Freedom of Information, Hydro One Inc., 483 Bay Street, 15th Floor, North Tower, Toronto, ON M5G 2P5.

If you have any questions or concerns about privacy at Hydro One, please contact our Privacy Office as follows:

Naomi Martin

| 

Adele Pantusa  
  
---|---  
  
Senior Legal Counsel

| 

Senior Legal Counsel  
  
Hydro One Inc.

| 

Hydro One Inc.  
  
TCT 15, Trinity Square

| 

TCT 15, Trinity Square  
  
483 Bay Street

| 

483 Bay Street  
  
Toronto, ON  M5G 2P5

| 

Toronto, ON  M5G 2P5  
  
Telephone: 416-345-6309

| 

Telephone: 416-345-6310   
  
Fax: 416-345-6972 

| 

Fax: 416-345-6972  
  
E-mail: [naomi.martin@HydroOne.com](mailto:%20naomi.martin@HydroOne.com)

| 

E-mail: [apantusa@HydroOne.com](mailto:apantusa@HydroOne.com)
